<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<docs>
  <doc id="solution">
    <desc>
      The System X System Library acts as the runtime library for Cmajor programs written for 
	  the System X platform. The System Library is written in Cmajor and can be compiled with the 
	  <a href="../tools/sxcmc/sxcmc.html">sxcmc</a> compiler just as Cmajor user
	  programs.
    </desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.Core">
   <desc>
      The System.Core module contains primitive types, operations for primitive types, intrinsic functions and intrinsic concepts known by the compiler.
      It does not have any source code.
   </desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.Base">
	<desc>
		The System.Base module contains basic facilities, containers, algorithms, and I/O.
	</desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.Lex">
	<desc>
		The System.Lex module contains lexical analyzer engine and lexing utilities.
	</desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.RegularExpressions">
	<desc>
		The System.RegularExpressions module contains a minimal implementation of a regular expression matching engine.
	</desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.Screen">
	<desc>
		The System.Screen module contains a library for writing character-based event-driven full screen terminal mode System X applications.
	</desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System">
	<desc>
	The System module acts as an umbrella module that references all other System Library modules.
    The System module is implicitly referenced by all user programs and libraries, so an explicit reference for any system library module is not needed.
    This library is linked with programs and libraries that have <strong>target=program</strong> or <strong>target=library</strong> in a <em>.cmp</em> file respectively.
	</desc>
  </doc>
  <doc id="System.Install">
	<desc>
	The System.Install module is a special module that takes care of installing the System libraries to cmajor/system-x/system/lib/&lt;config> directory.
	It contains no source code entities, but references the <ref>System</ref> module.
	</desc>
  </doc>
</docs>
